Guide to the Chinese Land Records, 1584-1978 EAL.2011.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Seller: 張國光 [ZHANG Guoguang] -- Buyer: 張國寶 [ZHANG Guobao] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民國17年, 民國24年 [1928, 1935] (Box 3, Folder 132)
- Seller: 昌宜 [Changyi] -- Buyer: 咸宜 [Xianyi] -- Place: 福建省（清源縣?） [Fujian Sheng (Qingyuan Xian?)] -- Personal, 民國17年 [1928] (Box 3, Folder 133)
- Buyer: 錆啇百壽協廳軒 [Qiangdi Baishouxietingxuan] -- Place: 福建省 [Fujian Sheng] -- Government, 民國17年 [1928] (Box 3, Folder 134)
- Seller: 道楷 [Daokai] -- Buyer: 咸宜 [Xianyi] -- Place: 福建省(清源縣?) [Fujian Sheng (Qingyuan Xian?)] -- Personal, 民國17年 [1928] (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Owner: 黃乞容 [HUANG Qirong] -- Place: 福建省永泰縣 [Fujian Sheng Yongtai Xian] -- Government, 民國17年 [1928] (Box 3, Folder 136)
- Owner: 盧亨雲 [LU Hengyun] -- Place: 福建省古田縣 [Fujian Sheng Gutian Xian] -- Government, 民國17年 [1928] (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Seller: 張國光 [ZHANG Guoguang] -- Buyer: 張國寶 [ZHANG Guobao] -- Place: unknown -- Personal, 民國17年 [1928] (Box 3, Folder 138)
- Owner: 林枝貴 [LIN Zhigui] -- Place: 福建省古田縣 [Fujian Sheng Gutian Xian] -- Government, 民國18年 [1929] (Box 3, Folder 139)
- Owner: 陳傳京 [CHEN Chuanjing] -- Seller: 陈成餘 [CHEN Chengyu] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民國18年 [1929] (Box 3, Folder 140)
- Seller: 程道魯 [CHENG Daolu] -- Buyer: 程楊春 [CHENG Yangchun] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民国18年 [1929] (Box 3, Folder 140A)
- Seller: 陳太記 [CHEN Taiji] -- Buyer: 陳宿漙 [CHEN Sutuan] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Personal, 民国18 年, 民囯20年, 民囯24年 [1929, 1931, 1935] (Box 3, Folder 140B)
- Seller: 陳宿康 [CHEN Sukang] -- Buyer: 陳桂修 [CHEN Guixiu] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民国18年,民国24年 [1929, 1935] (Box 3, Folder 140C)
- Owner: 洪國慶 [HONG Guoqing] -- Place: 福建省古田縣 [Fujian Sheng Gutian Xian] -- Government, 民國19年 [1930] (Box 3, Folder 141)
- Seller: 高天钏 [GAO Tianchuan] -- Buyer: 郑祚龙 [ZHENG Zuolong] -- Personal, 民国20年 [1931] (Box 3, Folder 142)
- Owner: 黃乞容 [HUANG Qirong] -- Place: 福建省永泰縣 [Fujian Sheng Yongtai Xian] -- Government, 民國20年 [1931] (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民國21年 [1932] (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Seller: 劉振萬 [LIU Zhenwan] -- Buyer: 劉紀臣 [LIU jichen] -- Place: 福建省閩清縣 [Fujian Sheng Minqing Xian] -- Government, 民國21年 [1932] (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Owner: 林可昌 [LIN Kechang] and 林可淦 [LIN Kegan] -- Personal, 民國21年 [1932] (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Seller: 欽源 [Qinyuan] -- Buyer: 陳欽瑞 [CHEN Qinrui] -- Place: 福建省福清縣 [Fujian Sheng Fuqing Xian] -- Personal, 民國21年 [1932] (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Seller: 陳聖榜 [CHEN Shengbang] -- Buyer: 陳桂修 [CHEN Guixiu] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Personal, 民国21年, 民国23年, 民国24年 [1932, 1934, 1935] (Box 3, Folder 147A)
- Owner: 余興泉 [YU Xingquan] -- Place: 福建省古田縣 [Fujian Sheng Gutian Xian] -- Government, 民國22年 [1933] (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Owner: 葉克培 [YE Kepei] -- Place: 福建省古田縣 [Fujian Sheng Gutian Xian] -- Government, 民國22年 [1933] (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Seller: 林述璋 [LIN Shuzhang] -- Buyer: 林學通 [LIN Xuetong] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民國23年 [1934] (Box 3, Folder 150)
- Seller: 黃懷周 [HUANG Huaizhou] -- Buyer: 邵李氏 [Shaolishi] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民國23年, 民國29年 [1934, 1940] (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Owner: 劉德桂 [LIU Degui], 劉德輝 [LIU Dehui], 劉如慶 [LIU Ruqing] and 劉景星 [LIU Jingxing] -- Place: 福建省建陽縣 [Fujian Sheng Jianyang Xian] -- Government, 民國24年 [1935] (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Seller: 陳如良 [CHEN Ruliang] -- Buyer: （陈？）謀丁 [(CHEN?) Mouding] -- Place: 福建省古田縣 [Fujian Sheng Gutian Xian] -- Government, 民國24年 [1935] (Box 3, Folder 153)
- Owner: 張國軒 [ZHANG Guoxuan] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 民國24年 [1935] (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Owner: 林親顶 [LIN Qinding] -- Seller: 陳佃 [CHEN Dian] -- Buyer: 施至祥 [SHI Zhixiang] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 民國24年, 1953年 [1935, 1953] (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Seller: 劉人科 [LIU Renke] -- Buyer: 劉子知後裔 [descendants of LIU Zizhi] -- Place: 福建省閩清縣 [Fujian Sheng Minqing Xian] -- Government, 民国24年 [1935] (Box 3, Folder 155A)
- Seller: 陳欽隆 [CHEN Qinlong] -- Buyer: 陳欽瑞 [CHEN Qinrui] -- Place: 福建省 [Fujian Sheng] -- Personal, 民國丙子25年 [1936] (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Seller: 陳欽隆 [CHEN Qinlong] -- Buyer: 陳欽瑞 [CHEN Qinrui] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Personal, 民國25年 [1936] (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Seller: 陳欽隆 [CHEN Qinlong] -- Buyer: 陳欽瑞 [CHEN Qinrui] -- Place: 福建省 [Fujian Sheng] -- Personal, 民國丙子25年 [1936] (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Seller: 陳欽隆 [CHEN Qinlong] -- Buyer: 陳欽瑞 [CHEN Qinrui] -- Place: 福建省 [Fujian Sheng] -- Personal, 民國丙子25年 [1936] (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Owner: 吳修晟 [WU Xiusheng] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 民國26年 [1937] (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Owner: 林施裕 [LIN Shiyu] -- Place: 福建省永泰縣 [Fujian Sheng Yongtai Xian] -- Government, 民國28年 [1939] (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Seller: 藍維乾 [LAN Weiqian] and 藍維坤 [LAN Weikun] -- Buyer: 吳淮棉 [WU Huaimian] -- Personal, 民國庚辰29年 [1940] (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Seller: 陳老鳳 [CHEN Laofeng] -- Buyer: 陳玉書 [CHEN Yushu] -- Place: 福建省 [Fujian Sheng] -- Personal, 民國30年 [1941] (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Owner: 張道興 [ZHANG Daoxing] -- Seller: 余傳荃 [YU Chuanquan] -- Buyer: 張道興 [ZHANG Daoxing] -- Place: 福建省閩清縣 [Fujian Sheng Minqing Xian] -- Government, 民囯31年, 民國32年 [1942, 1943] (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Owner: 黃昌聲 [HUANG Changsheng] -- Buyer: 陳智存 [CHEN Zhicun] -- Place: unknown -- Government, 民國32年 [1943] (Box 3, Folder 165)
- Seller: 黃炮 [HUANG Pao] -- Buyer: 沈秀清 [SHEN Xiuqing] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 民國32年, 1952年 [1943, 1952] (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Owner: 葉文怡 [YE Wenyi] -- Place: 福建省永泰縣 [Fujian Sheng Yongtai Xian] -- Government, 民國34年 [1945] (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Owner: 黃生官 [HUANG Shengguan] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國34年 [1945] (Box 3, Folder 168)
- Seller: 林明尊 [LIN Mingzun] -- Buyer: 陳功存 [CHEN Gongcun] -- Place: 福建省上竹林 [Fujian Sheng Shangzhulin] -- Personal, 民國34年 [1945] (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Owner: 黃克動 [HUANG Kedong] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國35年 [1946] (Box 3, Folder 170)
- Owner: 黃克動 [HUANG Kedong] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國35年 [1946] (Box 4, Folder 171)
- Owner: 黃森官等 [HUANG Senguan etc.] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國35年 [1946] (Box 4, Folder 172)
- Seller: 張學車 [ZHANG Xueche] -- Buyer: 陳書寶 [CHEN Shubao] and 張學車 [ZHANG Xueche] -- Place: 福建省福清縣 [Fujian Sheng Fuqing Xian] -- Government, 民國35年, 1951年 [ 1946, 1951] (Box 4, Folder 173)
- Owner: 王鐘鈞 [WANG Zhongjun] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 174)
- Owner: 王鐘鈞 [WANG Zhongjun] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 175)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 176)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 177)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xianen] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 178)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 179)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 180)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 181)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 182)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 183)
- Owner: 林修枝 [LIN Xiuzhi] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 184)
- Owner: 黃克動 [HUANG Kedong] and 黃生官 [HUANG Shengguan] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 185)
- Owner: 黃生官 [HUANG Shengguan] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 186)
- Seller: 陳潮寳 [CHEN Chaobao] -- Buyer: 陳敦清 [CHEN Dunqing] -- Place: 福建省林森縣 [Fujian Sheng Linsen Xian] -- Government, 民國36年 [1947] (Box 4, Folder 187)
- Seller: 黃榮森 [HUANG Rongsen] -- Buyer: 黃煌 [HUANG Huang] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 民國36年, 1952年 [1947, 1952] (Box 4, Folder 188)
- Owner: 余挹岩 [YU Yiyan] -- Place: 上海市 [Shanghai Shi] -- Property Charity bazaar letter, 民国37年 [1948] (Box 4, Folder 188A)
- Owner: 嬌世范 [JIAO Shifan] -- Place: 遼寧省新金縣 [Liaoning Sheng Xinjin Xian] -- Government, 民國38年 [1949] (Box 4, Folder 189)
- Place: 華東 [Huadong(East China)] -- Government, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 190)
- Seller: unknown -- Place: 福建省福州市 [Fujian Sheng Fuzhou Shi] -- Government, 民國38年 [1949] (Box 4, Folder 191)
- Seller: 林定宗（林登宗？） [LIN Ding(Deng)zong] -- Buyer: 余溪 [YU Xi] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 民國38年, 1952年 [1949, 1952] (Box 4, Folder 192)
- Seller: 劉隹 [LIU Zhui] -- Buyer: 沙延德 [SHA Yande] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 民國38年, 1952年 [1949, 1952] (Box 4, Folder 193)
- Owner: 王萃延 [WANG Cuiyan] -- Place: 福建省南安縣 [Fujian Sheng Nan'an Xian] -- Government, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 194)
- Owner: 黃生官 [HUANG Shengguan] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Government, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 195)
- Seller: 王細細弟 [Younger brother of WANG Xixi] -- Buyer:王炳凱 [WANG Bingkai] -- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian] -- Personal, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 195A)
- Owner: 林宗 [LIN Zong], 吳淑珍 [WU Shuzhen], 林涯 [ LIN Ya] and 林貢 [LIN Gong] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 196)
- Owner: 施性固 [SHI Xinggu], 顏蒜 [YAN Suan], 施能鎖 [SHI Nengsuo] and 施松柏 [SHI Songbai] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 197)
- Seller: 朱發 [ZHU Fa ] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 198)
- Seller: 孫宗馨 [SUN Zongxin ] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 199)
- Owner: 黃滑 [HUANG Hua], 黃嚕 [ HUANG Lu], 黃世 [HUANG Shi] and 連芳 [LIAN Fang] -- Place: 福建省南安縣 [Fujian Sheng Nan'an Xian] -- Government, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 200)
- Owner: 李水旺 [LI Shuiwang], 陳連玉 [CHEN Lianyu], 李義妹 [LI Yimei] and 李義草 [LI Yicao] -- Place: 福建邵武縣 [Fujian Sheng Shaowu Xian] -- Government, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 201)
- Owner: 李銀山 [LI Yinshan] -- Place: 四川省合川縣 [Sichuan Sheng Hechuan Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 202)
- Seller: 陳佃 [CHEN Dian] -- Buyer: 施至尚 [SHI Zhishang] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 203)
- Seller: 方圍九 [FANG Weijiu] -- Buyer: 林武 [LIN Wu] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 204)
- Seller: 陳佃 [CHEN Dian] -- Buyer: 施至尚 [SHI Zhishang] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 205)
- Owner:李文富 [LI Wenfu] -- Place: 雲南省鶴慶縣 [Yunnan Sheng Heqing Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 206)
- Owner: 藍福良 [LAN Fuliang] -- Place: 四川省榮縣 [Sichuan Sheng Rong Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 207)
- Seller: 陳佃 [CHEN Dian] -- Buyer: 施至尚 [SHI Zhishan] -- Place: 福建省晉江縣 [Fujian Sheng Jinjiang Xian] -- Government, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 208)
- Seller: 林清 [LIN Qing] -- Buyer: 陳蕃薯 [CHEN Fanshu] -- Place: 福建省東山縣 [Fujian Sheng Dongshan Xian] -- Government, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 209)
- Owner: 楊世平 [YANG Shiping] and 陳道祥 [CHEN Daoxiang] -- Place: 福建省順昌縣 [Fujian Sheng Shunchang Xian] -- Government, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 210)
- Place: 福建省 [Fujian Sheng] -- Government, Unknown (Box 4, Folder 211)
- Owner: 慎方 [Shenfang] -- Place: 福建省連城縣 [Fujian Sheng Liancheng Xian] -- Government, 道光？年 [1827-1850] (Box 4, Folder 212)
- Seller: 吳秉鑒 [WU Bingjian] -- Buyer: 謝 [XIE] -- Place: 福建省閩縣 [Fujian Sheng Min Xian] -- Government, Unknown (Box 4, Folder 213)
- Place: 福建省閩侯縣 [Fujian Sheng Minhou Xian], Unknown (Box 4, Folder 214)